- 嘿 Gary 最近咋样? - 这不是你...你的...
- Hey, Gary. How you doing? - Good, good. - So, He's not--oing? - This isn'tou Go.
- 他是我侄子 - 真可爱 我觉着
- He's my nephew. - Cute, I imagine.
跟你这么说吧 小孩 这里是张毛爷爷
I'll tell you what, kid. Here's a Jackson.
给你自己买十罐汽水 然后你从没见过我们
Go get yourself 10 sodas and you never saw us.
或者就是水 就买水吧
Or just water. Just choose water.
- 哇 这真奇怪不是么? - 嗯
- Wow, this is weird, huh? - Mm.
我已经好久没见到你们俩了 哇
It's been a long time since I've seen you guys. Wow.
你看到我发你的那些图片了吗?
Did you see those pictures that I sent you?
并没有 Gary 还有我们他妈的为啥要来这儿?
No I didn't Gary. And why the fuck are we here?
好吧 别激动别激动 这里不留名字的
Okay, easy, easy. It's anonymous.
就装作你们是父母来参观这个地方的吧
Just pretend like you're parents checking this place out.
- 画点什么吧 - 我甚至都不画自己的指甲 Gary
- Paint something. - I don't even paint my own nails, Gary.
一个越南女士来给我画的
A Vietnamese lady does that.
快说 不然我们就走了
Talk or we leave.
是关于家庭第一提案的
It's the Families First Bill.
对于总统来说这段时间很难过
It's a difficult time for the president.
Gary 我很擅长我的工作
Gary, I am very good at my job,
然而甚至连我都不能
And even I can't get
让民众投票给那个添油加醋不知何物的东西
People to vote for that heap of mystery meat.
不是这样的 恰恰相反 她想让这个法案消失掉
It's not that. It's the opposite. She wants it to go away.
所以Selina需要失去选票
So Selina needs to lose the vote
而你想让我们抓住最后的机会游说国会议员
And you want us to lobby members of Congress under the wire.
我真高兴我离开了 她已经完全变成女版Colonel Kurtz了
I am so glad I left. She has gone full Colonel Kurtz.
Colonel Kurtz:小说Heart of Darkness中一个擅长心理控制的角色
她是不是在桌子下面下命令?
Is she giving orders from under the desk?
她根本不知道这件事 好吗?
She doesn't even know about this, all right?
而且她不能知道这件事
And she's not gonna know about this.
啊 既然这样 那我就要对此表示同意
Okay, well, in that case, I'm gonna say yes to this,
- 但是仅仅为了一个原因 - 忠诚?
- but for one reason only. - Loyalty?
- 钱 - 你就不能为了Selina做这件事吗?
- Money. - Can't you just do this for Selina?
- 不行 - 哦 好吧 但是我无权答应这个啊
- No. - Okay, well, I can't authorize that.
好吧 那让Ben来
Well, get Ben to.
你怎么知道Ben也被扯进来了?
How'd you know Ben was involved?
- 真行 - 因为他没被扯进来
- Okay. - Because he's not.
- 对哦 - 这已经完全失去控制了
- Right. - This is getting completely out of hand.
不 不 没有
No, no, it isn't.
我们刚接受了你的请求
We just accepted your proposal
我们会和大人物保持交流的
And we'll be in touch with the figures.
噢 好吧 谢谢
Okay, all right. Thank you.
喂喂喂别 你想暴露我们的身份吗
No, no, no. You want to blow our cover?
没人在手工店里握手
Nobody shakes hands in a craft shop.
你要知道 这里起码有三个小孩是我的
You know, at least three of these kids are probably mine.
好吧
Okay.
今天对于Meyer总统来说是个大日子
A big day for President Meyer
因为她被围攻的家庭第一提案
As her beleaguered Families First Bill
终于到了最终投票阶段
Faces the final vote.
- 你在干啥呢? - 啥?
- What are you doing? - What?
为什么把花摆在在这个的前面?
Why are the flowers in front of it?
如果花在那儿的话我看不到了好伐
I can't see it if the flowers are there.
- 哦上帝 - 哦天哪
- Ugh, God. - Oh, God.
哦别 别 让我去拿 你个可爱的病号
No, no, let me get that, you sweet little invalid.
我不是病号 我完完全全好着呢
I'm not an invalid. I'm completely fine.
- 这些是空的 - 我都不知道我怎么感冒的
- These are empty. - I don't know how I got this.
大概是见了太多人了吧 我猜
From meeting people, I guess.
上帝 Gary 我真希望耶稣
God, Gary, I wish to Jesus
让你得流感而不是我
That you had gotten this flu instead of me.
哦上帝啊 我也这么觉得 我也是
Oh, my God, me, too. Me, too.
好啦 让我们开始吧
All right, here we go.
- 就放在那儿 - 哇哇哇哇
- Put it right there. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
她需要睡个小觉 她就睡个小觉
She needs to nap. She needs to nap.
并且这是一个Gary Walsh执行命令
And that is a Gary Walsh executive order.
- 记着了 - Gary 我好的天花乱坠 好吗?
- Duly noted. - Gary, I'm completely fine, okay?
我今天就在家工作了 哦上帝啊
I'm just working from home today. My God.
好样的 海湾干净了
Okay, coast is clear.
211个人会反对这项法案
211 are voting against the bill.
五个未决定 然后我们正在试图把三个支持的
Five undecided. And we've got three yeses
转换为反对的那一派
That we're working on turning around into nos.
所以不通过是在我们意料之中的
So defeat is within our grasp.
- 女士 - 嗯?
-Ma'am. - Yes?
这个iPad上有我喜欢的一个语音备忘录应用
Here's an iPad with that voice memo app I like.
上面还有一个特别酷的
There's also a cool
铺砖游戏 如果你想玩的话
tile game on here if you want to play a game.
- 啥?铺砖? - 当然 你不想玩的
- A what? A tile? - Which, of course, you don't want to play.
那是家庭第一提案么?
Is that Families First?
是的 很快要投票了 但是我们正在努力让它不通过
Yeah, it's really close, but we're doing our best to lose it.
我能表示一下知道这玩意让我的工作多困难吗?
Can I just restate how difficult me knowing this makes my job?
而且我的工作已经很困难了
Which is already extremely difficult.
我们不得不让这个法案不通过
We have to lose the vote
这样才有一丝机会来赢得竞选
To have a chance of winning the election.
我们砍掉这个法案 然后让舆论停止
We kill the bill, we end the criticism.
我可是媒体主管
I'm the press secretary.
我不知道的东西 我就不算撒谎
What I don't know, I can't lie about.
包括这个 不管是什么鬼的玩意
Including this, whatever this is.
你不需要对这个撒谎啊
You don't need to lie about this.
我们是在让民众投同意票啊
We're asking people to vote yes.
我们在干我们应该干的事
We're doing what we should be doing.
我们只是向糟糕的一面干罢了
We're just doing it badly.
- 噢! - 保佑你
- Oh! - Bless you.
我觉得我刚刚把我的一部分胰腺给打出来了
I think I just sneezed up part of my pancreas.
别担心 Mike 我们有一整队最糟糕的人在做
Don't worry, Mike. We have a team of our worst people on this.
Cazzelli, Lennox 还有那些蠢货 Jonah Richard
Cazzelli, Lennox. The usual saps. Jonah, Richard.
我啥也没听到 因为回音太响了
I didn't hear any of this because the acoustics are so bad.
Sue 这是一个测试备忘录
Sue, this is a test memo.
发送备忘录
Send memo.
- 这啥玩意? - 这是个小脚凳
- What is this? - It's a footstool.
哦是吗 我感觉好多了
Oh, yeah, I feel so much better.
先生 这是一个很棒的法案
Sir, this is a great bill.
并且有时候一个伟大的人才能见到其伟大之处
And sometimes it takes a great man to see greatness.
您是一个伟大的人吗?
Are you a great man?
标题四 第七部分
Title four, section seven
否定整个立法的意义
Negates the entire point of the legislation.
他们怎么写的这个鬼?
How did they write this thing?
喝醉了然后在脚底贴上蜡笔么?
Get drunk and tape crayons to their feet?
嗯 如果我告诉你那点已经取消了呢?
Well, what if I told you that was gone?
但是这没取消不是吗?
But it isn't gone, is it?
-你别想带他走 -他的肥屁股是我的
- You are not taking him. - His jittery ass is mine.
-喂 我就站在这儿呢 -抱歉
- Guys, I'm right here. - I'm sorry,
你的肥屁股是总统的
Your jittery ass is the president's.
你根本就不该来这 Jonah
You shouldn't even be here, Jonah,
除非你是为了科学研究来医院捐献大脑的
unless you're giving your brain to science.
我今天可是代表总统到这儿来的 Amy
I'm here on behalf of the president, Amy.
你还记得她吗？如果你那次没有发疯的话
Do you remember her? She's the woman that would have fired you
她是那个有权炒了你的女人
if you hadn't gone fucking Fukushima.
没错 我们今天是带着使命来的
That's right, we're on a mission.
我真的很惊讶啊 你们两个
I am surprised the two of you
当年竟然能从你们妈逼里生出来
even found your way out of your own mothers' vaginas.
哦 天啊 哥们 我出来的时候就他妈像知道地图一样
Oh, my God, dude, I got out of there like I had a fucking map.
是不是该考虑一下这位临终女士的感受呢？
How about a little bit of consideration for a dying woman?
哦 我还没临终呢 我只是来这做些检查的
Oh, I'm not dying. I'm just here for some tests.
好吧 都安静下来吧 等等 Pierce跑哪去了？
Okay, pipe down. Wait, where's Pierce?
等等 Amy呢？
Wait, where's Amy?
别 别 别 别走！
No, no, no, no! No, no.
-那就是Amy -操
- That's Amy. - Shit!
是啊 真是耻辱
Yeah, what a shame.
我们该用中指给你擦擦眼泪
We should use this finger to wipe your tears.
不 不 不 不 Dan 赶紧从我车里滚出来
No, no, no, no. Dan, get out of my car.
你觉得我想
Do you think I want to
上你这个“我的世界”（低画质游戏）里的破车吗？
be in this fucking Minecraft piece of shit?
我可是总统的特使
I am an emissary of the president
我强烈要求你从我的车里出来
and I demand that you get out of my car.
你个死基佬 你还没搞清楚状况吧?
You colossal fucking fanny pack. You don't get it, do you?
他们派你来只不过是因为他们知道你肯定会搞砸的
They only sent you 'cause they knew that you would fuck it up.
你太蠢了 你根本就
You're so stupid, you don't even
不知道他们在利用你的愚蠢
know that you're being used for your stupidity.
你在胡说 Dan 我从你眼里就能看出来
That's bullshit, Dan. I can tell from your eyes
因为这他妈的就是胡扯 Richard呢?
and because it's fucking bullshit. Where's Richard?
这件事还没完 Egan
This isn't fucking over, Egan.
-赶紧上来开车吧 小婊砸 -好的
- Just get in and drive, bitch. - Okay.
操
Shit.
-你他妈在逗我吗? -只是个小故障
- Are you fucking kidding me? - It's just a glitch.
-哦 这是你的车吧? -是的
- Oh, this is your car, right? - Yep.
看吧 弄好了
See? Fixed it.
好的
Okay.
你居然还倒车? 赶紧向前开啊
You're backing up? Just fucking go straight.
我上过精准驾驶课
I took a precision driving class,
Dan 我知道我在做什么
Dan. I think I know what I'm doing.
女士 没能联系上Pierce 抱歉
Ma'am, we've lost Pierce. I'm sorry.
我们应该派海豹突击队去
We should have hired Navy SEALs
而不是那两个人型笨海豹
instead of those two actual seals.
你们怎么能把一个大活人弄丢的?
How do you lose a whole person?
丢一个袖扣我能理解 人怎么能弄丢?
A cuff link I get, but not a person.
好的
Okay.
她说她说不出话来了
She said she's losing her voice.
刚听一个记者说
Just heard from a reporter who says Moyes
Moyes认为白宫
thinks the White House
雇了说客去搅黄自己的法案
hired lobbyists to destroy its own bill.
-哦 天啊 -老天
- Oh, my God. - Jesus.
好的 好的
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
她说你搞砸了 Ben
She said you fucked up, Ben.
你把Gary拉进这摊浑水我极其生气 你得把他安全的弄出去
And I'm mad as hell that you put Gary in the shit. You need to get him out.
-她没这样说 Gary -是的 她说了
- She didn't say that, Gary. - Yes, she did.
所有人都把臭嘴给我闭上！
Everyone, shut your fucking holes!
总统没有生病
The president is not sick.
有病的是你们 你们这些寄生虫
You guys are. You're parasites.
你们简直就是一群庸人式侵袭
You're like an infestation of mediocrity.
我才不在乎你是否是一个五十年代的电台广播员
I don't care if you're a 1950s radio broadcaster.
你是否是一个被撕烂
You're Fozzie Bear who's been ripped up
还曾走私过海洛因的福滋熊
and used to smuggle heroin.
一只喜欢说笑话的布偶熊
还有你 纳粹医生 而你 我他妈根本就不知道你是个什么鬼
A Nazi doctor. I don't even know what the fuck you are.
这与你们自己的利益无关
This is not about serving yourselves.
而是要为总统效力
This is about serving the president.
所以我们好好效力 行吗？
So let's do that, shall we?
-Tom -Tom
- Tom. - Tom.
-闭嘴 Gary -闭… 好的
- Shut up, Gary. - Shut... mm-hmm.
领导训话这种事得我来做 好吗?
?
do the team talks, okay?
您说得很对 女士
You're absolutely right, ma'am.
我赞成你刚才说的所有话
And I agree with everything you just said.
振作起来好吗 同志们！
So get it together, people!
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
找到Pierce
Find Pierce.
打电话给航空航天局
Call NASA.
他们的卫星
They've got to have a satellite
肯定能定位出一个脑残
that can pinpoint a moron.
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
如果你想抓住一个逃犯
If you want to catch a fugitive,
你就得站在逃犯的角度思考
You got to think like a fugitive.
-他会去哪？ -呃 机场
- Where's he going? - Uh, to the airport.
他为什么要去机场？
Why would he be going to the airport?
去赶飞机啊 Dan
To catch a plane, Dan.
你知道吗 你可以多踩两下油门的 Jonah
You know, you could just hit the fucking gas, Jonah.
Dan 我可不想被开罚单
Dan, I'm not getting a ticket.
这种事在以后竞选时
That's the kind of shit that
会给我带来麻烦的
comes back to bite you when you run for office.
是啊 那种事才会耽误你
Yeah, that's what's gonna hold you back.
好吧 车里的新规则 如果你的名字是D打头
Okay, new rule in the Cube. If your name begins with D,
你就得立即给我闭嘴
you need to shut the fuck up immediately.
没我什么事 因为我的名字开头是R
I'm fine because my name begins with an R.
-叫你的简称“混蛋”就有你的事了（Dick有混蛋的意思 也是Richard的简称） -好吧
- Not if we shorten it to Dick. - Well, I mean...
-哦 那个好像是Amy -在哪?
- Oh, I think that's Amy. - Where?
我的天 我他妈在后座都看见了
Jesus Christ, I'm in the back seat and I can fucking see her.
哦 在那儿呢 好的
Oh, right there. Okay, fine.
-议员先生 -哦 哇哦
- Congressman. - Oh, wow.
这可有点吓人啊 听着 我不是在躲你们 希望你能明白
Well, this is freaky. Look, I'm not hiding, just so you know.
好的 议员先生 是时候离开礼品店了
Okay, Congressman, time to exit through the gift shop.
好的 先生 你得跟我们走
Okay, sir, you're gonna have to come with us.
伙计们 我母亲现在病太严重了 我不能丢下她一个人
Guys, my mom is too ill to be left alone right now.
我是说 我现在丢下她一个人
I mean, I left her alone right now
是因为她喜欢看书
Because she likes to read.
当然她现在看不了 因为她病的很重
But she can't read right now because she's very sick.
可能会好转吧 也可能更糟
But she might get better. Or she might not get better.
- 有书陪葬她就安心了 - 她还没到奄奄一息的地步吧
- She could be buried with a book. - We know she's not dying.
- 她还在和病魔苦苦斗争 这是重点 - 她真棒
- She's a fighter, is the thing. - Good for her.
虽然再次说出这话有点诡异
As weird as it feels to still be saying this,
但总统希望你去白宫一趟
The president would like to see you at the White House.
我觉得我要重蹈覆辙 殒命于此了
I feel like I'm about to kick it old school and die in office.
巅峰之时却选择了放弃
Quitting on a high.
你觉得我这么做对吗?
Do you think I'm doing the right thing here?
我是说 这提案其实挺好的
I mean, this is a good bill.
尽管有些水分 但对民众的生活
Even watered down, I think it's gonna make a difference
是有所改善的
In people's lives.
您才是总统
Ma'am, you're the president.
轮不到我来告诉您该怎么做
It's not for me to tell you what to do.
对哦
Yeah.
估计还是否决了它比较好
Guess I should kill it.
没错
Is the right answer.
我冷
I'm cold.
这里有华氏110度(43摄氏度左右)了吧
It's actually about 110 in here.
一点也不暖和
There's no way it's warm in here.
- 你真觉得热? - 这里暖和得都可以种西红柿了
- Do you really feel warm? - You could grow tomatoes in here.
真的 无比的热
Honestly, it is unbelievable.
好吧 我可不能为了你而降温
Well, I can't make it cooler for you.
功劳是我们的
Well, we're taking the credit.
不 是我们的
No, we're taking the credit.
要不折中一下? 功劳全是我们的
How about a compromise? We'll take all the credit.
- 好吧 也许我们可以平分赏金? - 什么赏金?
- Well, perhaps we could split the bounty? - What bounty?
哼 我估计赏金是没有的 不过--
Well, I'm guessing there's no bounty, but--
Dan Amy 近来如何? 剩下的交给我吧
Dan, Amy, how are you? I'll take it from here.
- 我想带Pierce一起进去 - 哎 哎 不行 不行
- I want to take in Pierce. - Whoa, whoa. No, no, no.
我们不能为了这家伙
We are not going into the
进白宫暴露自己
White House and blowing our cover for this guy.
你不能进来 这是总统的命令
You can't come in. That comes from the president.
- 是吗 她这个婊砸 - 我会转告她你问好了的
- Well, she's a bitch. - I'll tell her you said hi.
嘿 我们得快点了
Hey, we got to get moving.
嗨 伙计们 好久不见
Hey, you guys. Long time no see.
不是吧 Mike 你也参与进来了?
Jesus, Mike, they got you involved in this?
你他妈的不是新闻发言人吗?
You're the fucking press secretary.
就是说啊 我也没想明白呐
Thank you. That's what I've been saying.
我也不想被卷进来的好不
I have no wish to be embroiled in this either.
这跟我的推诿本领可不搭
It doesn't sit well with my policy of plausible deniability.
快走吧 回见了
Let's get going. I'll see you around.
潜台词是 麻烦离我远点
And by that I mean please, stay away from me.
回见 阴魂不散的跟班们
See you later, ghosts of staffers past.
总统女士 我把议员Pierce带来了
Madam President, I brought you Congressman Pierce.
我也有帮忙 女士 在下Richard Splett
I brought him also, ma'am. Richard Splett.
她知道你们是谁 你们可以走了
She already knows who you are. You can go.
不 不 不 不是说你 不是说你
No, no, no. Not you. Not you.
我们可是你的死忠粉
We're such big fans.
我是您的头号粉丝 谢谢您 总统女士
I'm a big fan of yours. Thank you, Madam President.
谨听您指示 需要我做什么吗?
I am here to serve. How can I help?
总统想请你帮个忙
The president needs you to do something for her.
作为交换 她想给你换个更好的工作
And in exchange, she feels that you deserve a better job.
- 没错 - 谢谢
- Yes. - Thank you.
大使 这个职位听起来怎样?
Ambassador, perhaps. How does that sound?
大使? 我吗?
Ambassador? Me?
噢 哇哦 和我想象的不太一样啊
Oh, wow. Not what I was expecting.
你最喜欢哪座城市?
What's your favorite city?
达拉斯 我最喜欢德克萨斯州的达拉斯市了
Dallas. I love Dallas, Texas.
不行 得是国外的城市
No, it needs to be a foreign city.
噢 对哦 大使嘛 当然了
Oh, of course. Ambassador. Right.
嗯 巴黎 可以吧?
Um, well, Paris, right?
我爱巴黎 虽然我没去过 但那里看起来很棒
J'adore Paris. I've never been, but it looks amazing.
- 不 - 不行 那里不行
- No. - No, that's not gonna happen.
- 哦 好吧 - 你有没有其他...
- Oh, of course. - Do you have another...
呃 我喜欢澳大利亚 或新西兰
Well, I love Australia. Down under.
总统希望你对
And the president needs you to vote no
今晚的议案投否决票
On tonight's bill.
你们...
Are you guys...
你们--不是在开玩笑吗?
Are you-- are you serious?
好吧 总统 她想让我否决她自己的提案?
Okay, the president, she wants me to vote against her bill?
- 怎么我看起来很蠢吗? - 是的
- Am I being stupid here? - Yes.
是的
Yes.
不是 我的意思是 你- 不是 你看起来并不-
No. I mean, you're-- no, you're not being--
我是说 没错 你要投否决票
It's, yes, you need to vote no.
好 我可以-很乐意
Okay, I can-- love it.
虽然不知道你们在说什么 但是好的
- Don't get it, but it's all right.
我只是想帮上忙
I just want to help.
不过 记得告诉我 我会被派去哪里就好了
But, yeah, just let me know where I'm going.
- 你现在就想知道? - 对 这样最好
- You need to know now? - Yeah, that would be great.
您觉得呢 女士?
What'd you say, ma'am?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
- 她说不了话 - 嗯
- Her voice is gone. - Yeah.
她能说出我要去的地方吗?
Was she able to say where I'm going?
我就职的地方?
My posting?
啊哈 嗯哼
Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你可以去巴黎
You can have Paris.
什么? 我能去巴黎?
- What? - I can have Paris?
- 哇哦 谢谢 - 不 不 不用
- Wow, thank you. - No, no, no.
- 巴黎 - 恭喜
- Paris. - Congratulations.
- 谢谢 - 别忘了投票
- Thank you. - Don't forget to vote, all right?
-  好 好 好 好 - 不 不
- Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. - No. No.
不 不 我是说 好 我投否决票
No, no. I mean, yes, I'm voting no.
刚刚睡着了
It's an "Otter."
没事 女士 Pierce答应投否决票了
No, ma'am, Pierce went to vote.
他还觉得自己会去巴黎
And then he thinks he's off to Paris.
我说- 我说了巴黎不行
I said-- I said no to Paris.
我们会在投票后给他打电话 告诉他是去摩加迪沙
We'll call him after the vote, tell him it's Mogadishu.
他刚刚可以随便乱说
He literally could have said anything.
刚才那一瞬间 Gary成了世上最有权势的人
For a moment, Gary was the most powerful person in the world.
听起来挺有趣 给我弄点汤来
That's hilarious. Get me some soup.
好
Yep.
问题是 众议院会通过本次修订法案吗?
The question is, will the House pass the bill as amended?
-此次投票限时十五分钟
- This is a 15-minute vote.
老天爷啊 屁股打那一针真是要了命了
Oh, my God. My ass is killing me from that shot.
但我感觉身体好多了
But I feel pretty good.
真的?
Really?
总统夫人 - 怎么了?
Ma'am. - What?
天呐 开始了
Oh, boy. Here we go.
这感觉就像我希望自己的孩子能顺利的生下来
It's like I want my baby to live.
我不想自己的孩子胎死腹中
I don't want my baby to die.
我们还是就把它看做一条法案吧
Maybe think of it more of as a bill,
这个比喻最真实的贴近了法案
which in a very real way is what it is.
- 恩 - 到Pierce了
- Mm. - There's Pierce.
他连走路都那么呆
He even walks dumb.
每次我看到他 都仿佛能听到马戏团的音乐声
Every time I see him, I hear circus music.
要给力啊Owen 这是你发光发亮的时刻
Come on, Owen. It's your time to shine,
你倒霉催的破灯泡
you dim fucking bulb.
- 他投了否决票 提案没通过 -哦!
- He voted no. We lost the vote. - Oh!
我们成功地失败了
We are victorious in defeat.
我们可以短暂地兴奋一下
We may allow ourselves a brief period of rejoicing.
好吧 我的提案被否了
Okay, so I lost the vote.
我输了提案 但却赢了这一场
I won by not winning.
天啊 我真是百感交集
God, I don't know how I feel.
且不说 我现在感觉像一只浣熊在我脑袋里拉了坨屎
Apart from, like, having a raccoon take a shit in my head.
您应该感觉棒棒哒 夫人
You should feel great, ma'am.
这是一场实实在在的 至关重要的胜利
That was a solid, important defeat.
- 我要先去把衣服换了...
- I'm gonna go change my clothes... -
...跟全国观众发几句牢骚 然后再回到床上歇着去
...croak to the nation, and then I'm going back to bed.
这样不错
This is good.
Moyes威胁要去议会
Moyes is threatening to go to the floor
要求给今天发生的一切来个官方彻查
for an official investigation into what happened today.
- 糟糕透了 -嗯哼
- This is bad. - Mm-hmm.
我也是其中的一份子 那是不是意味着我也受到牵连了?
I'm in the middle of this. Does this mean I'm implicated, too?
这样吧 就算是也跟我说不是
You know what. Just say no even if it does.
Gary 你说过你是重要的一环 这我可以证明
Well, Gary, you said you were important. I can testify to that.
Ben 既然这是你说过的
Ben, this is one of those
那些小波折是不会发生的
little hiccups that you said was not gonna happen,
那我就把这事留给如此能干的你了
so I'm gonna leave this in your capable hands.
Mike 你要像从未
Mike, you have to deny
撒过谎一样 去否认这件事
this like you've never denied anything before.
就是撒谎咯? 我一直以来避免去做的事?
So lie? The one thing I've been trying not to do?
听着 我不会让你做连我自己都做不到的事
Look, I wouldn't ask you to do anything I wouldn't do myself.
其实刚才这句话是假的 你习惯习惯吧
nd while that isn't true, find some comfort in it.
好了 Gary -别找我!
Okay, Gary? - Nope.
在不久的将来 我会在国会之前
I will work on putting forward a new, streamlined
送上一份新的且更为完善的Families First Bill
Families First Bill before Congress in the near future.
她的声音像是Bob Dylan在水下唱歌
She sounds like an underwater Bob Dylan.
很难听懂她正在说什么
It is actually quite difficult to understand what she's saying.
...即将面临灾难性气候的孩子们
...children from impending climate Armageddon.
这没准儿是个好事
Which may be a good thing.
天佑美利坚
And God bless America.
好 信号切出
And we're out.
感谢你 夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
好吧-- 哦
Okay-- oh.
好 谢谢了伙计们 万分感激
Okay, thank you very much, guys. Appreciate it.
呼 好冷啊
Ooh, it's cold.
你们可以明天再来取这些东西吗?
You think you could just pick this shit up tomorrow?
可以 -好的 夫人
Ma'am. - Yes, ma'am.
哦 神呐
Oh, God.
去你妈蛋的 美利坚
Fuck you, America.
您有十四条未听语音备忘录
You have 14 new voice memos.
我的天
Oh, my God.
Mike 一些老高尔夫球运动员死了
Mike, some old golfer died.
我需要发表点什么言论吗?
Do I need to say something?
下一条语音
Next memo.
Kent 我刚拿到你的文件
Kent, I just got your document.
我完全不明白这说的都是什么鬼
I have no idea what any of this means.
下一条语音
Next memo.
噢 好吧Kent
Oh, okay, Kent.
我才发现术语表 忽略我上一条语音吧
I just found the glossary, so ignore that last message.
下一条语音
Next memo.
Kent 我刚看了术语词汇表
Kent, I just read the glossary.
我完全不明白这说的都是什么鬼
I have no idea what any of it means.
这就是为什么我把另一份术语表也放了进去
That's why I included the second glossary.
下一条语音
Next memo.
Mike 我给你留的这些语音
Mike, is it pissing you off
是不是已经让你烦爆了
I'm leaving all these messages?
- 是的 - 下一条语音
- Yes. - Next memo.
很好 因为你一条
Good, 'cause it's pissing me off
都不回复我也把我气爆了
you're not answering any of these messages.
下一条语音
Next memo.
你是怎么做到睡觉时也在留言的?
How do you leave a memo in your sleep?
- 回见 - 下一条语音
- See you. - Next memo.
Mike 你今天上班了吗?
Mike, were you at work today?
我不记得看到过你
I don't remember seeing you.
下一条语音
Next memo.
Ben Moyes在问东问西
Ben, Moyes is asking questions.
这不会发展为任何一种形式的调查 对吗?
This isn't gonna lead to any kind of an investigation, is it?
语音已删除
Memo deleted.
我特么的希望不是
I fucking hope not.
你是否庄严宣誓你即将指证的所有证词
Do you solemnly swear the testimony you are about to give
均为事实真相 完整的真相
is the truth, the whole truth,
且只有真相 此事千真万确?
and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
千真万确
So help me God.
-是的 - 我发誓
- Yes. - I do.
- 我发誓 - 我发誓
- I do. - I do.
-是的 我发誓 - 必须的
- Yes, I do. - Absolutely.
- 没 先生 它还在里面 - 不过万一它没了呢?
- No, sir, it's still there. - But what if it was gone?
- 哦 那是个好主意 - 谢谢
- Oh, that's a good point. - Thank you.
所以你们就是白宫能给出的最好提议人吗?
So you're the best the White House has to offer?
- 是的先生 - 两个穿着老爹西装的巨型小孩
- Yes, sir. - Two giant children in their dads' suits.
嗯 先生 我们这里有一整个文件夹的数据
Uh, sir, we have a folder full of numbers here,
然后我觉得你会觉得这些数据
And I think you'll find these numbers
就是特别特别棒的数据
Just to be great, great numbers.
这数据说明了啥?
Saying what?
- 呃 Richard 这些数据说明了什么?
- Uh, Richard, what do the numbers say?
- 你都没读这些数据么?
- You haven't read the numbers.
我们就瞄了一眼数据 先生
We've glanced at the numbers, sir,
我瞄的第一眼就觉得它们特别非常有说服力了
And at first glance they are very compelling.
- 你们知道门在那儿 - 先生 如果有任何--
- You know where the door is. - Sir, if there's anything--
哦 等下 你们为Meyer总统工作
Oh, wait. You work for President Meyer.
你们不知道门在哪儿 我来告诉你
You don't know where the door is. I'll show you.
- 已经结束了 - 先生 你可能不知道
- It's over here. - Sir, you may or may not know
我经营着一个值百万美金的网站
That I ran a multimillion-dollar website.
所以如果我能提供各种网页设计或者支持...
So if I can offer any web design or support...
先生 我们能问你今晚会怎么投票吗?
Sir, can I ask you how you're going to vote today?
- 不能 - 不能是在说我们不能问你还是说你--
- No. - Is that no as in I can't ask you or no as in--
嘿 Sue 你见到我的包了吗
Hey, Sue, have you seen my bag?
哇哇哇 这里发生什么事了
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's going on?
这里是我的地盘 她需要静养 出什么事了?
This is my area. She needs quiet. What's going on?
把这个放在角落里就好 谢谢
Put it right there in the corner. Thank you.
不不不 你不能这样做 不能这样
No, no, no. You can't do this. You cannot do this.
Sue 我需要你在我房间外面
Sue, I need you to set up an office
设立一个办公室
outside the bedroom.
好的
Okay.
你不是唯一一个重要的人 Sue
You're not the only one who's important, Sue.
Gary
Gary.
能给我带杯加柠檬跟蜂蜜的热水吗?
Can I have a hot water with lemon and honey?
看到没?
See?
你应该去拿水了 Gary
You should get on that, Gary.
啊 我知道
Uh, I know.
所以 Tom 你对我们总统感觉如何?
So, Tom, how are you finding our president?
呃 你知道 像总统一样的
Oh, you know, presidential.
感觉像是她要管理整个国家似的
It's like she wants to run the whole damn country.
你知道吗? 之前那货 他也是这样的
You know what? The last guy, he was the same way.
我们同意她要继续当总统
We agreed she's gonna stay president.
我们必须得做一切来停止这个法案
We have to do everything we can to stop that bill.
所以你会么?
So are you?
你要知道 这句话开始说的是“我们”
You know, you just started that last sentence with a "We"
然后你以“你”来结束了这句子
And you finished it with a "You."
你有什么进展么?
Are you making progress?
是 我在弄 我让Richard和Jonah--
Yeah, I'm on it. I got Richard and Jonah--
哦 Ben 我不需要知道你在干嘛
Ooh, Ben, I don't need to know what you're doing.
我只需要把这玩意搞定
I just need to get it done.
超级 超级大的撕逼 连新郎都被卷进去了
Huge, huge fight. Even the bride got involved.
- 不会吧 - 简直棒呆了
- No. - Amazing.
波士顿的婚礼就是这么帅气
There is nothing like a Boston wedding.
- 让我给你讲讲 - 哇 刚刚那简直是让我担忧的棒 Tom
- Let me tell you that. - Wow, that was worryingly good, Tom.
我是指 刚刚那可是柔道黑带级别的扯淡啊
I mean, that was some black belt jujitsu bullshit right there.
我得走了 我们需要在八分钟之内解决掉它
I have to go. We'll take this up in eight minutes' time.
- 你可以进去了 - 你不能进去
- You are clear to go in. - You can't go in there.
Kent 你可以直接进来
Kent, you can come straight in.
如果Gary试图阻止你 你可以无视他
If Gary tries to stop you, you can ignore him.
好吧 她发给我个备忘录说需要休息
Well, I have a memo saying that she needs rest.
- 你的是什么时候收到的? - 你的是什么时候收到的?
- When was yours sent? - When was yours sent?
我先问的
I asked you first.
我得看看我的手机
I'll have to check my phone.
女士 我知道这很难
Ma'am, I know it's
特别是当你在管理一个自由国家的时候
difficult when you're running the free world,
但是你真的需要去休息一下
But you should really get some rest.
是 或者我可以去换个新的医生
Yeah, ahem, or maybe I can get a new doctor.
既然这样 那我就建议您要一直喝水了 女士
In which case I'll just say keep taking the fluids, ma'am.
Moyes投反对票 好消息...
Moyes is voting no. Good news...
对于别人来说
For the other side.
- 这简直太糟糕了 - 是啊是啊
- That's so bad. - I know, I know.
- 太糟糕了 - 是的
- So bad. - Yeah.
你知道Moyes吗? 这简直太不可思议了
Have you heard about Moyes? It's incredible...
有些人的怎么这么目光短浅 难以置信
How shortsighted some people can be. Unbelievable.
难以置信 我们就在说这个
Unbelievable, that's what we were saying.
- 我之后再来看你 女士 - 哦 谢谢
- I'll check back on you later, ma'am. - Okay, thank you.
啊咳
Ahem.
好 恭喜你女士 Moyes这事太棒了
Okay, congratulations, ma'am. So great about Moyes.
我们只需要四个反对票 你的法案就砍了
We're now only four votes away from killing your bill.
我感觉我像是泰坦尼克号的船长
I feel like I'm captain of the Titanic
然后那个冰山是我自己凿出来的
And I carved out the iceberg myself.
好的 女士 我觉得你需要睡一个修身养心的觉
Okay, ma'am, I think you need to take a little power nap.
- 你需要休息 好吗?
- You need to rest, okay?
- 是的 我觉得我也应该去睡会
- Yeah, I think maybe I'm gonna rest.
- 是的 就放松一下身体 - 对
- Yeah, just rest your body. - Yeah.
女士 你准备好参加下一个会议了吗?
Ma'am, are you ready for your next meeting?
- 国防部长到了 - 哦 那我就不睡了
- SecDef is here. - Okay, no.
没关系的 我可以在我死翘翘的时候长眠
It's okay. I can sleep when I'm dead
大概就在一个小时之后
In about an hour.
家庭第一提案简直就跟翔一样
There is nothing good to be said about Families First.
自从Herod之后就没有任何立法
Not since Herod has there been a piece of legislation
能这样摧毁中产阶级家庭了
So damaging to average families.
先生 如果你想帮助家庭的话 这不是你想要的提案
Sir, if you want to help working families, this is not it.
这就感觉像是用一对勺子
This is akin to carrying
给你做心脏手术差不多
out heart surgery with a pair of spoons.
我不需要被两匹游说马来骑着 还引导我说
I don't need to be ridden by you two lobby horses
这个提案是大肠中的排泄物
To know that this bill is a waste of bowel space.
- 啊 那太棒了 - 太好了
- Well, that's great. - Fantastic.
能在政治活动里见到一个
It is nice to meet somebody in politics
知道自己说什么的人来换换心情 可真是开心
Who knows what he's talking about for a change.
啊 议员
Yeah, Congressman, I'm
我就把这些数据留给你
Just gonna leave you now with some numbers.
顺便剧透一下 它们加起来还不对数
And spoiler alert, they do not add up.
这跟Jonah Ryan给我的文件夹一样
This is the same folder that Jonah Ryan had.
等下 你见到Jonah Ryan了?
Wait, you met with Jonah Ryan?
六英尺长的蜡像和他那个可亲可爱的男盆友?
Six-foot waxwork and his  boyfriend?
- 那应该是他了 - 所以你们不为白宫工作
- That would be him. - So you don't work for the White House,
除非这么说"婊砸" 或者其它类似的这种
Unless it's like "Bitch" Or something like that.
- 对不起 - 借过
- I'm sorry. - Excuse me.
感谢您为国效命
Thank you for your service.
刚才的会议怎么样 先生?
How was the meeting, sir?
非常有效率
Very productive.
这简直像政治卡通片里面一样
It's like something out of a political cartoon.
什么 你是说不好玩吗
What, you mean not funny?
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
Moyes是他妈怎么跑到两个名单上的?
How the hell did Moyes end up on two lists?
我说过了 Ben
I made it clear Ben
应该把他名单上的所有变动都给我过目的
should run all his list alterations past me.
才不是 我的名单才是总名单 你的不过是子名单
No, mine was the master list. Your list was a sub-list.
它是子名单 也就意味着它是详细的特殊情况名单
It was a sur-list, which means over-list.
- 哦 草泥马 - 你的耳屎能放倒一位总统
- Oh, fuck you. - Your earwax could bring down a president.
而我当时其实一点都不想见到Dan和Amy
And I didn't even want to see Dan and Amy.
可现在他们想要钱
And now they're expecting money.
- 我不知道会这样 - 钱? 什么钱?
- I didn't know that. - Money? Money?
Gary 我才是唯一能批钱的人
Gary, I said access only.
是 现在我们只能把活动专款拨出一部分来用
Yeah, now we're gonna have to divert funds
这已经构成金钱欺诈
From the campaign and that's fraud.
于是我们又得销毁证据
And then we're gonna have to destroy the evidence
结果就成了有预谋的欺诈
And that's conspiracy to commit fraud.
不对 有现金交易记录就会对我们非常他妈的不利
No, a cash trail is very fucking bad for us.
- 喔 - 嘿 先别急着走 当月猛男
- Oh. - Hey, hold on there, Hunk of the Month.
我要是玩完了 你也一样
If I'm going down, you're going down, too.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't know what this is about.
问得好 Dan和Amy
Good point. Dan and Amy.
他们要拿到的现金
They're getting paid cash
是从为砍掉这个提案的那部分 竞选活动筹款里来的
From the campaign fund to bring down the bill.
从这儿 你就已经跳进黄河洗不清了
There, you've been blooded.
所以加入流氓圈 握紧老二
So join the circle jerk. Grab a dick.
我挺希望自己能听清
Wish I could hear what you
你在这没完没了的钻孔的声里说了什么
Were saying over that incessant drilling sound.
你干嘛呢? 小声点! -
What are you doing? Shh! -
什么现金?
What cash?
Dan和Amy什么?
What Dan and Amy?
Ben要付钱给Dan和Amy 让他们去游说反对法案
Ben's paying Dan and Amy to lobby against the bill
现在留下了交易记录 我们都会被控告
And now there's a cash trail and we're all incriminated.
但你不会
But you're not.
哦 天啊 现在你也会了!
Oh, my God, now you are!
干得好
Well done.
现在我感觉真是好多了
Now I feel a lot better.
你之前知道这事吗 Tom?
Did you know, Tom?
夫人 我和您一样震惊
Ma'am, I am as shocked as you are.
既震惊 又失望 Ben
Shocked and disappointed, Ben.
夫人 Moyes会投票支持那个法案
Ma'am, Moyes is voting yes.
Ruiz也是
Ruiz is voting yes.
现在还剩最后一票 我们需要Pirece议员
This comes down to one vote. We need Congressman Pierce.
我的未来就掌握在那个傻逼家养小精灵手上?
My future depends on that dumb fucking elf?
天惹-- 他人在哪?
Jeez-- where is he?
我为你能这么勇敢而感到骄傲
I'm so proud of how brave you've been.
我本来想找点洁肤液 但他们没有--
I was looking for some lotion, but they didn't--
你好 Pierce议员 Pierce夫人
Hello, Congressman Pierce, Mrs. Pierce.
我们从白宫来
We are here from the White
想讨论下关于第一家庭提案的事
House on behalf of the Families First Bill.
哦 好的 妈 白宫的人来看我了
Oh, yes. Mom, the White House here to see me.
我们需要你为提案投票
We need you to vote for the bill.
更重要的是
More importantly,
总统需要你为它投票
the president needs you to vote for the bill.
总统? 她让你们来找我?
The president? The president sent you here to talk to me?
她在话语中提到了你的名字
She used sentences containing your name.
好的 我加入 呃 我是说 当然没问题
Okay, I'm in. I mean, yeah, absolutely.
- 太好了! - 妈 总统夫人需要我去--
- Fantastic! - Mom, the president needs me to--
哦 不 我们被小丑和企鹅抢先了
Oh, no, Joker and Penguin beat us to it.
嘿 伙计们 你们来得正好 可以一起庆祝
Hey, guys. You're here just in time to celebrate.
议员先生将会
The congressman is
为家庭第一提案投赞成票
going to vote yes on the Families First Bill.
这是总统的私人请求 所以...
It was a personal request from the president, so...
议员先生 现在 虽然我尊重您的决定
Congressman, now, while I respect your decision,
你知道这项法案的修正案会
You do understand that the amendments to this bill
对你的行政区造成不利影响吧
Will negatively affect your district.
努力工作的家庭不会愿意出钱支持懒人的
Hardworking families don't want to support lazy ones.
而你的支持率将会缩得
And your support will shrink
比泡在十二月哈德逊河里的小弟弟还快
Faster than a penis in the December Hudson.
- 真的吗? - 你们这群吃屎的吹箫侠
- Really? - You shit-eating cocksuckers.
- 冷静 冷静 - 我很抱歉
- Whoa, whoa! - I'm sorry,
Pierce夫人 你怎么敢跑到这里
Mrs. Pierce. How dare you come in here
来试图强迫一个人投票
And try to strong-arm a person
他可是正在自己生病的母亲床边呢
When he's sitting at his sick mother's bedside?
这明明是你刚才做的事 傻逼
That's exactly what you just did, dumbass.
用不着你告诉我 我做还是没做什么事
Don't tell me what I did or did not just do.
能不能请你们把声音放小一点?
Could you guys please keep the noise down?
这层楼还有很多病重的人
There's a lot of really sick people on this floor.
对 的确 我现在就看到有两个人病得不轻
Yes, there are. I see two very sick people.
那两个
Those two.
好吧 夫人 我刚刚和Amy通过话了
All right, ma'am, I've just spoken to Amy.
她还有Dan正在医院 Pierce在那看望他的母亲
Her and Dan are with Pierce and his mom at the hospital.
- 但是路上堵车了 - 额滴神啊
- But there's been a holdup. - Oh, God.
她大概打算死也要刁难我
She's probably gonna die just to spite me.
那个坏婊子
That evil bitch.
Richard 和Jonah也在那边
And Richard and Jonah are there.
要我说都怪Kent还有Bill
And I blame Kent and Bill for that.
喔 真是作了一手好死啊
Well, this is a long glass of frozen strawberry fuckup.
嘿 听着 Ben 你得做点什么
Hey, listen, Ben, you've got to do something.
我可不想为D区囚犯里最壮的那个收保护费啊
I don't want to be a bagman for the toughest guy in D block.
- 好了 别说了 Gary - 好了 听着 把Pierce带到这儿
- All right, stop it, Gary. - Okay, look, get Pierce here.
懂了嘛? 现在马上
Okay? Right now.
现在我得掌控这个
I'm gonna take control of this situation
我什么都不知道的局势 对吧?
That I don't know anything about, right?
因为我看上去是唯一一个...
Because I am the only one who seems to be...
- 有能耐的
- Capable.
- 喔 天
- Oh, God.
有没有什么可能帮您止咳?
Is it possible to stop coughing?
没有!
No!
但有相同的数字统计 嗯 现在我倒有兴趣了
But you have the same numbers. Well, now I'm interested.
老子现在太他妈有兴趣了
Now I am deeply fucking interested.
我们和他们用一样的办公文件夹
We have the same Office Depot folder as they do.
给"华盛顿邮报"打电话 我嗅到了阴谋的味道
Call the "Washington Post." I smell conspiracy.
好的 可以 为啥这个人像猫王一样抖腿?
Okay, sure, so why is this one shaking like Elvis's leg?
你知道 我愈发感觉
You know, I'm starting to get the feeling
副总统想让自己的提案失败
That Meyer wants her own bill to fail.
我觉得我又想重新投回赞成票了
I think I've just reboarded the vote yes express.
Meyer是个代行职务的总统
Meyer is a stand-in president.
你不觉得是时候找一个更有资格的人了吗?
Don't you think it's time we have someone who is qualified?
总统之所以有资格成为总统
The president is qualified
因为她就是总统
To be president because she is president.
你们党派中有已经是总统的竞选人了吗?
Does your party have a candidate who is president?
我喜欢这个
I like that.
谢谢 女士 再次感谢您能参与进来
Thank you, ma'am. And again, thank you for joining us.
哦 不客气 谢谢 嗯
Oh, you're welcome. Thank you. Ahem.
我们需要讨论一下Tom要戴什么颜色的领带
We need to discuss the color of tie that Tom's gonna wear
不好意思 女士 你说什么? 我没
I'm sorry, ma'am. What was that? I didn't
哦 哦 我就是发一个备忘录
Oh, no, I was just sending a memo.
我不想一直打扰你们
I didn't want to keep interrupting all the time.
真是思虑周全 谢谢
That is very considerate. Thank you.
没有什么能够管理经营一个文明社会
This is no way to run a civilized society.
- 我相信 - 那是什么?
- I believe - what is that?
总统发来的备忘录
It's a memo from the president.
- 你继续 这无关紧要 - 这很重要 Ben
- Go ahead, it's not important. - It is important, Ben.
我发的每个备忘录都重要
Every memo I send is important.
发送备忘录 天惹
Send memo. Jesus.
我没收到任何备忘录
I'm not getting any memos.
- 哦 现在我收到了
- Oh, now I am.
继续 Tom
Go ahead, Tom.
好的
Okay.
好吧 参议员 重新回到我的
Well, Senator, to return to my
就算这样 你也必须得表现的强势点  懂吗？
And you've got to be aggressive, though, you know?
拿出点男子气概
Man up here a little bit.
- 强势点? - 是的
- Be aggressive? - Yeah.
我要开始真生气了 参议员
I'm starting to get really angry, Senator.
我愈发感觉
I'm starting to feel that
你没有认真听我说 参议员
You're not really listening to me, Senator.
而且我受够了你持续地打断我
And I'm getting sick of your constant interruptions.
什么鬼? Moyes投赞成票?
What the fuck? Moyes is voting yes?
Moyes应该投反对票 应该反对
Moyes was 100% no. Moyes was a no.
Ben Moyes本应该坚决投反对票的
Ben, Moyes was supposed to be 100% no.
就这样吧  我办了个辩论会 你赢了 假装反对
That's it. I'm throwing the debate. You win, pretend opponent.
等一下
Wait a second, Kent
Kent有一个Jonah和Richard名列其中的会见名单
had a list who Jonah and Richard were seeing
而你有一个Dan和Amy名列其中的会见名单？
And you had a list who Dan and Amy were seeing?
你没想过把两个名单对比一下吗?
Did you not think to compare the lists?
我还有一个名单而且把你列在首位 Gary
I have another list and you're right at the top of it, Gary,
所以别他妈质疑我的工作方法
So don't you dare try to question my fucking methods.
好吧 我在另一方面
Well, I on the other hand,
极度质疑你的狗屎方法
Do dare to question your fucking methods.
好吧 Kent和我
Well, Kent and I were
负责行动的不同部分
running different parts of the operation.
所以你的人
So your people are going
会和Jonah与Richard见相同的人?
To see the same people as Jonah and Richard?
一个 就一个相同的人
One. One of the same people.
哦 一个 所以一个就没问题
Oh, one. So one's okay.
我们可以向超级碗现场只投放一枚核武器
We just let off one nuke at the Super Bowl.
哦 所以你要微观干涉
Oh, so now you want to micromanage
一些和你压根不想管的事情
Something that you didn't even want to be involved in.
我没想干涉 但是你不觉得
I don't want to manage it, but don't you think
我们能找一个有能力的人来做吗?
We could maybe find someone competent who could?
好了 不管是什么 我不需要知道
Okay, whatever it is, I don't need to know.
我来告诉你出什么事了
I'll tell you what's going on.
Jonah早先去见了Moyes 然后Dan和Amy也去见了他
Jonah saw Moyes earlier today and Dan and Amy have, too.
现在Moyes已经知道我们的意图了
And now Moyes is onto us.
你为啥告诉我?
Why did you just tell me that?
这对我来说更糟糕
This is so much worse for me.
我就是分配给Dan和Amy任务的那个一线特工
I was the field agent who gave Dan and Amy the mission.
我就是那信使 我可能要被射杀了
I was the messenger. I could be shot.
这和你无关 Gary
This isn't about you, Gary.
天惹 这里没有你任何鸟事
Jesus, nothing here is ever about you.
我什么也没听到
I didn't hear any of this
因为我耳鸣很严重
cause I have a really bad case of tinnitus
特别是在讨论道德层面有疑问的事情的时候
Especially when discussing morally dubious things.
所以像是一种选择性罪孽耳鸣症
So it's kind of like sinnitus.
但我还是会受到牵连 我是关键环节
But I'm implicated. I'm the linchpin.
- 我可能要去改造了! - 闭嘴!
- I could go to jail! - Shut up!
不 你闭嘴 你也闭嘴
No, you shut up. You shut up.
而我也会最先闭嘴
And I will also shut up first.
Sue! Sue 我要见总统
Sue! Sue, I need to see the president.
她在开参谋长联席会议 Gary 很重要的事吗？
She's in with the joint chiefs, Gary. Is it that important?
听着 Sue 我卷入了点麻烦
Listen, Sue, I'm involved with some stuff here.
那种能让你死翘翘的可怕麻烦
Scary stuff like take it to your grave kind of stuff.
就是那样 那就是我喜欢的
And that's the that's the way I like it.
好吧 呃 她五分钟之内出来 能等一下吗?
Okay, well, she'll be out in five. Can it wait?
恩 没问题 好的
Yeah, no problem. No problem.
如果他要是调查我们卧底的事情呢？
What if he checks our cover story?
例如 如果他询问议会?
Like, what if he informs Congress?
Dan 他就是个议员
Dan, he's a congressman.
国会议员永远不会言行一致
Congressmen never do anything they say they're gonna do.
- 这事你怎么能不抓狂?
- How are you not freaking out about this?
我还挺乐在其中 我喜欢卧底这事儿
I'm kind of having fun. I like having a cover story.
让我像查理的天使一样炫酷
Makes me feel like a Charlie's Angel.
天噜 太刺激了!
God, it was a rush!
对 但你是一个控制狂
Yeah, but you're a control
可这事已经失控了
Freak and this whole thing is out of control,
所你怎么还不抓狂?
So why aren't you freaking?
放松 终于有机会乐一乐 别管我
Relax. I'm finally having fun. Let me.
天惹 你知道嘛 我一直觉得以前的Amy
Jesus, you know, I always thought the old Amy
是个神经质婊 但我现在有点想她了
was kind of an uptight bitch, but now I sort of miss her.
你知道 如果说我神经质 那你就得罪我了
You know, if I was uptight, I'd be offended by that.
其实 你确实得罪我了 你不该叫别人婊砸
In fact, I am offended. You shouldn't call people bitches.
你以后不要做了哦
You shouldn't do that anymore.